Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Clipping file, ca. 1920-1980
Bentley Historical Library
- University of Michigan
  - U
    - Union-Activities.
      - 1948-1955 (Box 56)
      - 1956- (Box 56)
    - Union-Art exhibits.
    - Union-Forums. (Box 56)
    - Union-League Merger Proposals.
      (see: University Activities Center (1963-1965).)
    - Union Creative Arts Festival.
      (see: Union-Activities (through 1964). From 1965-see: University Activities Center.)
    - Union Fair.
    - Union Opera (Box 56)
      (1956 name changed to MUSKET ad became coed)
    - Unionization of Employees.
      (see: Employees. United Fund Drive. see: Charities.)
    - United Nations.
      (For United Nations Day and Week Celebrations, see: Student Government Council (Include university and Ann Arbor); Earlier celebrations see: Foreign Students; Foreign Students-International Center. For mock UN see: Political Clubs-International Relations.)
    - United Service to China.
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies-Asia. For other forms of relief to China, see: Foreign Students and Visitors.)
    - United States...
      - * in World Affairs (1947)
      - * in the World Crisis (1951).
    - Universalist Student Group.
    - Universities Space Research Association (A consortium).
    - University Activities Center.., 1963-1965
      (Includes discussion leading to merger of Union and League Activities (1963-1965).)
    - University Activities Center, 1965-
      (Est. June 1965 by merger of Union and League activities. For earlier material, see: Union-Activities; Women's League Activities.)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 56)
      - 1965-1967 (Box 56)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 56)
      - 1970-1973 (Box 56)
      - 1973- (Box 56)
    - University Bicentennial Committee (U.S. Bicentennial) (Box 56)
    - University Christian Federation.
      (see: Religion-University Christian Federation.)
    - University Club of Ann Arbor.
      (Includes the University Club Room at the Michigan Union. see: Societies-Faculty.)
    - University College. (Box 56)
    - University Concert Band.
    - University Day. (Box 56)
    - University Events Building.
      (see: Athletics-Building Program.)
    - University Hall.
    - University High School.
      (see: Education, School of-University High School.)
    - University Lecture Committee.
    - University List Scholarship Plan.
      (Tuition scholarships set up for Michigan high schools. see Scholarships.)
    - University Lutheran Chapel.
      (see: Religion-Churches-Lutheran.)
    - University Microfilms, Inc. (Relationship to University of Michigan).
      (see: University Microfilms, Inc. (General Vertical File).)
    - University Museums.
    - University Musical Society.
    - University of Michigan Club of Ann Arbor.
      (see: Alumni-MiU Club (AA).)
    - University of Michigan Press. (Box 56)
    - University Philharmonia.
      (see: Orchestras. University Press Club. see: Press Club.)
    - University Publications Office.
      (see: Publications. This Office was organized December 1, 1960. It consolidates the activities of the Office of Official Publications-University Press, the Office of Special Publications-University Relations, and the Faculty Directory.)
    - University Relations Service. (Box 56)
      (For releases see also departments concerned and University Record. For Development Council see: Finance-Alumni Aid.)
    - University Research Club.
      (see: Societies-Research Club of U. of M.)
    - University Safety Committee. (Box 56)
    - University Steering Committee on the Development of Academic Opportunities
      (see: Race Relations. Superseded in 1951Broy the Coordinating Committee for Human Relations Programs.)
    - University String Quartet.
      (see: Stanley Quartet.)
    - University System (of study).
      (see: Honors Program.)
    - Untermeyer Lectures.
      (Sponsored by the Dept. of Engineering English (Mr. 1939 1940). see: Engineering, College of (Admin.).)
    - Upper Atmosphere Research.
      (see: Engineering, College of-Engineering Research Institute (for material before 1958)-Space Research (for material 1959--).)
    - Upper Room Bible Classes
      (see: Religion.)
    - Urban Corps
    - Urban Journalism Workshop
    - Urban Studies. For material before, 1968 (Box 56)
      (see: Architecture and Design, College of.)
    - Use of campus buildings
      (see: Service Enterprises.)
    - Utilization of Human Resources (Research Project)
      (see: Research; Institute for Human Adjustment.)
    - Utilization of Scientific Knowledge, Center for Research on
  - V
    - Vandenburg (Arthur H.) Lectureship
    - Vanguard Club
      (see: Political Clubs-Vanguard Club.)
    - Varsity Men's Glee Club
    - Varsity Night
      (see: Bands-Varsity Night.)
    - Vesper services
    - Veterans. (Box 56)
      (Before 1952 see: World War II-Servicemen, Discharged. see also: Veterans-Societies.)
    - Veterans-American Veterans Committee (AVC). (Box 56)
    - Veterans-Dances.
    - Veterans-Societies. (Box 56)
      (Includes Veterans Wives Club, Ball and Chain (wives club), Women Veterans Association., Air Force Officers Women's Club. Air Force Officers Women's Club, Air Force Association, P-T Veterans Association, American Legion, U.S.O. dances. see also: Veterans-American Veterans Committee (AV); Veterans Organization (VO) American Legion.)
    - (Michigan Student)-Veterans Organization (VO). (Box 56)
      (see also: United States-Veterans Admin.-Hospitals)
    - Veterans Readjustment Center (Also called Neurosis Center) (Box 56)
    - Veterans Service Bureau. 1942-51-
      (see: World War II-Servicemen, Discharged; 1952-(see: Veterans.)
    - Victor Vaughan Medical Society
    - Victory Ball
      (see: Junior Hop.)
    - Vielle Trio
    - Viet Nam Policy, 1964-
    - Visa (Discount sales program)
    - Vision Research Lab. (Box 56)
    - Visitors.
      (Generally handled by the Guide Service, see: University Relations Service. For foreign visitors see also: Foreign Visitors. For faculty speakers see: the name of the department or faculty sponsoring.)
    - VISTA.
      (see: Peace Corps.)
    - Visual Instruction Institute
      (see: Extension-Audio-Visual Education Center.)
    - Vocal Music, see cards for: Music School of; Glee Clubs; Music, School. of-Extension Projects.
    - Vocational Education and Practical Arts, Dept. of. (Box 56)
    - Vocational Education Institutes
    - Vocational Guidance.
      - 1916-1939 (Box 56)
      - 1940- (Box 56)
    - Vocational Guidance Project (Flint)
      (see: Sociology, Dept. of.)
    - "Voice"
      (see: Political Clubs-Students for a Democratic Society, ("Voice" is a local chapter of SDS).)
    - Voice Department
      (see: Music, School of. see also: Opera; Choirs; Students, Outstanding-Music; Television; Radio; and other glee clubs and vocal groups.)
    - Volunteers in Service to America (VISTA)
    - Voting (Student)
      (see: Elections-National, State and Local. Includes question of students registering as Ann Arbor residents.)
    - Voyageurs, Les
    - Vulcans
      (see: Societies-Vulcans. see also: Societies-Engineering (for earlier senior eng. society called Web and Flange).)
  - W
    - War Department Laboratory
      (see: Engineering, College of.)
    - Waseda University (Japan) Institute for Research in Productivity. Waseda-Michigan Technical Agreement
    - Washtenaw County Community Mental Health Center
    - Water Pollution Research. (Box 56)
      (Includes federal lab. on North Campus. see also: Great Lakes Research.)
    - Water Resources and the Law
      (see: Law School-Institutes.)
    - Wayne State University (Joint Programs)
      (see: Joint Programs-Wayne State University.)
    - Weather station
      (see: Geology, Dept. of.)
    - Web and Flange (early Senior Engineering. Honorary)
    - Webster Dictionary.
      (Gift of Oreon E. Scott to seniors for scholarship, citizenship and participation 1955-see: Seniors.)
    - Weller (Carl V.) Lecture
    - Wesleyan Guild and the Wesley Players
      (see: Religion-Churches-Methodist.)
    - West Quad Glee Club
      (see: Glee Club-Misc.)
    - Westminster Student Fellowship, see; Religion-Churches-Presbyterian.
    - Whimsies.
      (see: Student Publications-Literary. (v.1-4 1921-4 Succeeded by Inlander).)
    - White (Edward H. II) Memorial Fellowship and Medallion
      (see: Engineering, College of-Aeronautical and Astronautical.)
    - Wig and Robe Ball
      (see: Law School-Dances.)
    - Wildlife Management, Dept. of
    - Willow Run Airport
      (see: Engineering, College of-Aeronautical.)
    - Willow Run Association for Neighborhood Development NRAND).
      (see: Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations.)
    - Willow Run Laboratories
      (see: Engineering, College of-Engineering Research Inst.; Institute of Science and Tech.)
    - Willow Run Village
      (see: Housing (Veteran's housing projects).)
    - "Willowhoppers". Bus service by Wolverine Club
    - Wilson (Woodrow) National Fellowship Foundation. (Box 56)
      (Begun as National Woodrow Wilson Fellowship program in 1945 at Princeton. Partially supported by the Ford Foundation. Moved to University of Michigan and changed to present title in 1957.)
    - Winter Weekend (1965-). (Box 56)
      (Includes Sesquigras (1967). see also: Spring Weekend.)
    - Wolverine Club
      (see: Athletics-Societies; Athletics-"Pep".)
    - Wolverine Cooperative Exchange.
      (Became Michigan Wolverine Restaurant, see: Cooperative Rooming and Boarding Projects)
    - Wolverine Derby
    - Woman in the World of Man
      (see: Summer Session-Campus Events (1954)-)
    - Woman's Athletic Association
      (see: Athletics-Woman's Athletic Association)
    - Women.
      (See also MiU Center for Continuing Education for Women; MiU Daycare Center)
      - 1911-1938 (Box 56)
      - 1939-1943 (Box 56)
      - 1944-1954 (Box 56)
      - 1955-March 1971 (Box 56)
      - April 1971-April 1972 (Box 56)
      - April 1972-1974 (Box 56)
      - August 1974- (Box 56)
    - Women. Committee of Advisors. (Box 56)
    - Women of the University Faculty.
      (a group of faculty women above the rank of instructor. Social group. see: Societies-Faculty.)
    - Women. Penny Carnival. (Box 56)
    - Women's Aeronautical Association.
    - Women's Assembly Association
    - Women's Education Club
    - Women's Glee Club
    - Women's Judiciary Council.
      (An Associated organization of the Women's League. (House Rules set up by the League Board of Representatives and punished by each house until 1934). Includes Women's Panel (for formulating new rules). see also: Dean-Women. (From 1940-46-6 also ran petitioning system for the Women's League).)
      - 1925-1955 (Box 56)
      - 1956- (Box 56)
    - Women's League,., 1920-1954
      (Present set-up of the Women's League). Women's Senate. (Replaced old Board of Representatives. Repres. from all main women's organizations). League (Executive) Council. (smaller group that actually runs the Women's League). Administrative Committees: (5) Junior Girls Play; Sophomore Cabaret; Women's League-Activities (includes Dance Class Comm. (see: League Bldg. for most of their dances: and Social Committee).; Women's Joint Judiciary; Associated Organizations: (5) Assembly; Sororities-Panhellenic; Athletics-Women's Athletic Association; Glee Clubs. (Women's Glee Club-here); Michigan Daily (Women's Page run as Association organization). The League Building is separate. For items concerning it see: League Building; League Building-Social Activities; Alumnae Council; League Building-Lydia Mendelssohn Theater.)
    - Women's League 1890-. (Box 57)
      (Includes officers, organizations, freshman orientation, membership drives, petitioning and elections, Installation, Merit (or Point) System, constitution, Board of Representatives, League Council, Women's Senate, delegates to National organizations, scholarship program, Buro-Cats and activities workshop. Includes these committees: Undergraduate Campaign Fund, House, Interviewing and Nominating, Personnel, Publicity. Women's League-Activities; Women's Joint Judiciary (for House rules); Junior Girls Play; Sophomore Cabaret; Assembly (associated organ.); Sororities-Panhellenic (Association organ.); Athletics-Women's Athletic Association (Association org.); Glee Clubs (Women Glee Club Association organ.); Michigan Daily (Women's Page Association organ.); League Building; League Building-Social Activities.)
    - Women's League-Activities,., 1920-1954
      (Includes social: dances, tea room, candy booths, travel bureau, bazaar, reading club, debates, workshop lectures. Includes service: Merit-Tutorial, Community Services Comm, World Fellowship, American Friends. Includes publications: League Lowdown, League Lantern (for rules, publications see: Women's Joint Judiciary. For activities of WW2 by Women's War Council, see: .Women's League. see also: League Building-Social Activities. (For Campus Casbah, joint act. with the Union held there and related groups.); University Activities Center, (1965-);)
      - 1890-1933 (Box 57)
      - 1934-1944 (Box 57)
      - 1945-1949 (Box 57)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 57)
      - 1952-1954 (Box 57)
      - 1955 (Box 57)
      - 1955- (Box 57)
    - Women's League-Activities merger with Union (Box 57)
    - Women's League-American Friends. Also called American Sisters.
      (see: Women's League-Activities.)
    - Women's League-House Organizations
      (see: Women's League. Women's League-House Rules, see: Women's Joint Judiciary.)
    - Women's League-Interviewing and Nominating Comm.
      (see: Women's League. (From 1940-6 petitioning handled by Women's Joint Judiciary).)
    - Women's League-Merit System (Point System)
    - Women's League-Merit-Tutorial
    - Women's League-Publications.
    - Women's League-Women's Panel. Set up by Dean of Women to examine House Rules
      (see: Women's Joint Judiciary.)
    - Women's Liberation
      (see: Activism; Birth Control (general file); Abortion (general file.); Day Care Center.)
    - Women's Research. Club
    - Women's Self-government Association
    - Women's Senate
    - Women's Student Government
    - Women's War Council
    - Wood Technology, Dept. of
    - Wood Utilization Lab.
      (see: Forestry; Natural Resources, School of (Became Dept, of Wood Technology, 1950).)
    - (University) Woodwind Quintet
    - Work Shops
    - Work-Study Program
      (see: Employment of Students; Dearborn Campus.)
    - Workers educational service
      (see: Extension-Workers educations Service.)
    - World Cooperation Week
      (see: Foreign Students.)
    - World Day of Prayer
      (see: Religion-University Christian Federation. For lectures not sponsored by a specific group, see: Religion.)
    - World Federalists
      (see: Political Clubs-United World Federalists)
    - World Fellowship
    - World Student Service Fund (WSSF)
      (see: World Warn-Relief.)
    - World University Fund Drive
      (see: Student Religious Organization (1957-).)
    - World War I
      (see also: Peace Movements. (American Student Defense League, see: World War).)
    - World War II.
      (see also: Under specific subjects as much material has been kept there, e.g., Campus opinion; Engineering. School; Hospital, etc.)
      - 1939-December 7, 1941 (Box 57)
      - December 8, 1941-1946 (Box 57)
      - 1946- (Box 57)
    - World War II.-Administrative policy (Box 57)
      (see also: Ruthven, A. 1942)
    - World War II.-Army and Navy Educational Programs
      (this includes E.R.C."Y" programs and Army and Navy groups stationed here). (see also: UROTC; ROTC: W.W. Military Service)
      - 1941-April 1943 (Box 57)
      - May-December 1943 (Box 57)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 57)
      - 1946 (Box 57)
    - World War II.-Bomber Scholarship Plan
      (see: W.W.-War Bonds.)
    - World War II.-Conscientious Objectors (E.S.M.D.T., etc.) (Box 57)
    - World War-Curriculum
      (see also: names Schools and Depts.)
      - 1941-1942 (Box 57)
      - 1943 (Box 57)
    - World War II.-3rd term plan (Box 57)
      (see also: Daily Special no. 5/15/42)
    - World War II-E.R.C.
      (see: W.W.II Army or Navy Educational program; World War II-Manpower Corps. see: WWII Student;)
    - World War II-Military and Naval Service.
      (Includes selective service and active duty). see also: WWII Army' and Navy educational program; NROTC: ROTC; also under Faculty-(individual).)
      - 1940-1942 (Box 57)
      - 1943 (Box 57)
      - 1944 (Box 57)
      - 1945 (Box 57)
    - World War II-Physical Education
      (see also: Athletics)
    - World War II-Post-War Planning and training (Box 57)
      (see also: Hou)
    - World War II-Relief
      - 1941-1949 (Box 57)
      - 1950 (Box 57)
    - World War-Service Men, Discharged
      (Includes MiU run Veterans Service Bureau, Veterans University Council, Armed Forces Information Center, etc. see also: Veterans-Societies; For 1952-see: Veterans.)
      - 1942-1945 (Box 57)
      - 1946 (Box 57)
      - 1947-951 (Box 57)
    - World War II Student Participation. (Box 57)
      (Non-Military, i.e. Manpower Corps, Hospital aides, etc.) see also: Student Life; Women)
    - World War II-"V" programs.
      (See: WWII-Army and Navy educational programs.)
    - World War II-Veterans.
      (see: WWII-Servicemen, Discharged; Veterans; Housing. also: Postwar planning and training;)
    - World War II-War Bonds. (Box 57)
      (Includes Bomber Scholarship). see also: Campus Events 1940-6)
    - (Bomber Scholarship)-W.W.II-War Bonds.
    - (Army Educational Program)-
      (see: World War II-Army and Navy Educational programs.)
    - (Berlin, Free Univ. of)
      (see: World War II-Relief.)
    - (Division for emergency Training)
      (see: World War I1-Admin.)
    - (Free University of Berlin)
      (see: World War II-Relief; Scholarship;-Foreign Student: -Student Govt.; Exchange Program)
    - Worm Runner's Digest
    - Woytinsky (W.S.) Lectureship Award. (Box 57)
    - Wrestling and Boxing. (Box 57)
    - Wright Committee on Communications Media
      (see: Publications. Writer-in-Residence.)
    - Writers Conference (Box 57)
    - Wyvern
      (see: Societies-Wyvern.)
  - X, Y, Z
    - Xi Psi Phi. Professional Dental Fraternity
      (see: Dentistry, School of.)
    - YMCA-YWCA (Box 57)
      (see: Young Men's Christian Association)
    - Yoakum
      (see: Administration.)
    - Yost (athletic) Honor Awards
      (see: Athletics (some earlier ones in prizes and Awards).)
    - Young Americans for Freedom
    - Young Communist League
    - Young Democrats
    - Young Friends Fellowship
      (see: Religion-Churches-Friends Society)
    - Young Lawyers Seminar
    - Young Men's Christian Association
      (Includes YWCA. see also: Student Christian Association)
    - Young People's Socialist League, see card for: American Student. Union.
    - Young Progressive Citizens of America
      (see: Political Clubs-Progressives.)
    - Young Republicans
    - Young Women's Christian Association
    - Zarafontis Foundation
    - Zeta Phi Eta
    - Zoo
    - Zoology, Dept. of (Box 57)
    - Zoology Club
      (see: Zoology Department.)
    - Zweit Lectures
      (see: Mathematics, Dept.)
    - Zwerdling Lectures. (Box 57)
- Faculty
  The Faculty files are physically interfiled under "F" in the University of Michigan series, but for desrcipitve purposes have been broken out as a separate series.
  - Faculty-A.
    - A-AL (Box 15)
    - AM-Az (Box 15)
    - Abbott, Waldo (Box 15)
    - Ackley, Gardiner (Box 15)
    - Adams, Henry Carter (Box 15)
    - Adams, James P. (Box 15)
    - Adams, Randolph G. (Box 15)
    - Aiton, Arthur S. (Box 15)
    - Aldridge, John (Box 15)
    - Alexander, John (Box 15)
    - Allen, Shirley W. (Box 15)
    - Allen, Francis A. (Box 15)
    - Anderson, Henry C. (Box 15)
    - Angell, Carleton W. (Box 15)
    - Angell, Robert C. (Box 15)
    - Arthos, John (Box 15)
  - Faculty-B.
    - B-BAK (Box 15)
    - BAL-BAR (Box 15)
    - BAS-BAZ (Box 15)
    - BE-BEL (Box 15)
    - BEM-BERO (Box 16)
    - BER-BEZ (Box 16)
    - BI-BL (Box 16)
    - BO (Box 16)
    - BR-BROW (Box 16)
    - BROWN-BRUC (Box 16)
    - BRUD-BURR (Box 16)
    - BURS-BY (Box 16)
    - Bachmann, Werner E. (Box 16)
    - Bacon, Deborah (Box 16)
    - Baier, Louis A. (Box 16)
    - Bald, F. Clever (Box 16)
    - Baldwin, DeWitt C. (Box 16)
    - Balzhiser, Richard (Box 16)
    - Bank, Theodore (Box 16)
    - Barker, Ernest F. (Box 16)
    - Bartell, Floyd Bartlett, Harley (Box 16)
    - Bassett, Leslie (Box 16)
    - Bates, Henry M. (Box 16)
    - Bates, Marston (Box 16)
    - Baxter, Dow V. (Box 16)
    - Beeuwkes, A. (Box 16)
    - Bell, Margaret (Box 16)
    - Bennett, Wells I. (Box 16)
    - Berry, Wallace (Box 16)
    - Bidlack, Russell (Box 16)
    - Bishop, William W. (Box 16)
    - Bishop, William W. (Publications) (Box 16)
    - Bishop, William W. Jr. (Box 16)
    - Blakeman, Edward (Box 16)
    - Blatt, Josef (Box 16)
    - Blood, Robert O. (Box 16)
    - Bloomer, Harlan (Box 16)
    - Boak, Arthur (Box 16)
    - Bolt, Jay (Box 16)
    - Bond, Floyd A. (Box 16)
    - Boston, Orlan W. (Box 16)
    - Boulding, Kenneth (Box 16)
    - Boyce, Ernest (Box 16)
    - Brandon, Arthur (Box 16)
    - Brazer, Harvey E. (Box 16)
    - Bredvold, Louis B. (Box 16)
    - Bretton, Henry L. (Box 16)
    - Briggs, Robert P. (Box 16)
    - Brigham, George B. (Box 16)
    - Brinkerhoff Js wet (Box 16)
    - Bromage, Arthur and Mary (Box 16)
    - Brown, Everett S. Brown, George G. (Box 16)
    - Brown, Marilyn Mason. (Box 16)
      (see Mason, Marilyn)
    - Brownell, Lloyd (Box 16)
    - Brumm, John L. (Box 16)
  - Faculty-C
    - C-CAM (Box 16)
    - CAN-CAZ CE-COG (Box 16)
    - CON-COOK (Box 16)
    - COOL-CRA (Box 16)
    - CRF-CU (Box 17)
    - Cabot, Hugh (Box 17)
    - Cain, Stanley (Box 17)
    - Cameron, George G. (Box 17)
    - Campbell, Oscar J. (Box 17)
    - Carr, Lowell (Box 17)
    - Carrothers, George (Box 17)
    - Carver, Harry C. (Box 17)
    - Christian, Palmer (Box 17)
    - Cicerone, Ralph (Box 17)
    - Clark, John (Box 17)
    - Clark, John A. (Box 17)
    - Clover, Elzada (Box 17)
    - Cohen, A-Z (Box 17)
    - Cohen, Wilbur J. (Box 17)
    - Culler, Frederick (Box 17)
    - Conn, Jerome W. (Box 17)
    - Conrad, Lawrence (Box 17)
    - Cooley, Charles H. (Box 17)
    - Cooley, Mortimer E. (Box 17)
    - Cooley, Thomas M. (Box 17)
    - Cooper, A-Z (Box 17)
    - Copley, Frank 0. (Box 17)
    - Courte, Robert (Box 17)
    - Couch, Richard B. (Box 17)
    - Cowden, Roy (Box 17)
    - Craig, A-Z (Box 17)
    - Craine, Lyle (Box 17)
    - Crane, A-Z (Box 17)
    - Crawford, Ivan C. (Box 17)
    - Crisler, Herbert 0. (Box 17)
    - Crosby, Elizabeth (Box 17)
    - Cross, Arthur Lyons (Box 17)
    - Curtis, A-Z (Box 17)
    - Curtiss, A-Z (Box 17)
    - Curtis, Herber D. (Box 17)
  - Faculty-D.
    - D-PAY (Box 17)
    - DB-DE (Box 17)
    - DI-DOR (Box 17)
    - DOS-DZ (Box 17)
    - Dana, Samuel T. (Box 17)
    - Davenport, A-Z (Box 17)
    - Davis, Calvin O. (Box 17)
    - Davis, Charles M. (Box 17)
    - Davis, H. Chandler (Box 17)
    - Davis, Joseph Baker (Box 17)
    - Davis, James M. (Box 17)
    - Dawson, John P. (Box 17)
    - Dawson, A-Z (Box 17)
    - Day, Edmund E. Dennison, David (Box 17)
    - Densmore, G. E. (Box 17)
    - Dewey, John (Box 17)
    - Dice, Lee (Box 17)
    - Dickinson, Z. Clark (Box 17)
    - Dingman, Reed O. (Box 17)
    - Dinka, Stephen. (Box 17)
    - Dodge, Stanley (Box 17)
    - Donahue, Wilma (Box 17)
    - Dorr, Harold M. (Box 17)
    - Dorr, John A. Jr. (Box 17)
    - Doughty, Richard M. (Box 17)
    - Dow, William G. (Box 17)
    - Duey, Philip (Box 17)
    - Duffendock, Ora (Box 17)
    - Dumond, Dwight (Box 17)
    - Dunham, Arthur (Box 17)
  - Faculty-E
    - EA-EF (Box 17)
    - EG-EZ (Box 18)